[{"answer": "What's the first thing, man? What's the first thing you're gonna do", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Hell you haven't", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You're GONNA be there! We're getting outta here! TAKE IT", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "YOU TELL HER", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Gotta be ten degrees out there", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Negative five", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Provisions! We are not leaving that motel room again till after New Year'", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "THIS MAN... has not had a cookie in two goddamn years! Get him two of everything", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You can't find... what", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Toys for... adults", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Baby, I'm gonna go tell 'em not to disturb us for the rest of the year. I get back in that room, you better be wearing nothing but a candy cane", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, lover. I'll see what you can do", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Since my friend moved in... my friend... he's come over more and more. To the apartment. my friend's the divorced one, 'member, with the tit job", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He read the letters, my friend. Some day I wasn't there. He went through my room. He found your letters", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How much money's in that casino? Da", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "The hell you don't", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I did", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What the fuck are you talking about", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "We'll trust you when we're rich. Why not", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "They run routes mostly east, retail stuff, warehouses. But my friend knows some guys in that place, that place, guys he helps get guns to that place. Hides 'em with his regular loads", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No. He wants to be working for himself someday", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, so how'd you hear about this place, then. Wor", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Prison?", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "We'll get there, baby... we'll get there..", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Shh, now. Rest now. Two years, my friend. You haven't had cranberry buns in two years", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You saved my life.  You could have run, but you didn't. You saved me", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I saved you because I love you, my friend.  Why'd you save me", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I've been doing good, though", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Didn't have to send me down a fucking mountain", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't know where you're going. But I'm going home", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Well. I'm going home", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "That is my card, guy. My card", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "He didn't hit.  You didn't hit. You're not hitting", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Paid the Alamo ten bucks to put the shiv in me. He's a lifer, what does he care. Paid a hospital guard fifty to put out the story I was dead. Once the wound healed up...  Got out of the Mountain this morning. And tonight I'm a rich man", "docId": "Reindeer-Games.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Do what", "qsentId": 36}]